Finding Aid for the Doris Fleming Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Travel Materials
  - Great Britain - Cambridge, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Great Britain - brochures - Devon, Shakespeare Country, English Lakes, Scotland, Harlech Castle, Merioneth, Wales; 12 photographs of London (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Great Britain - map and automobile association publications and receipts during travel (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Great Britain - “Worcester and its Cathedral”; “the Story of Romsey Abbey”; “Walk Round Guide to the Cathedral Church of Winchester”; Postcard of “The Thetcher Tombstone” at Winchester Cathedral (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Great Britain - official guide Old Sarum, Wiltshire; Companion to Salisbury Cathedral “Change and the Unchanging” (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Greece - postcards - Athens Acropolis, Delphi, and sculpture (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Greenland and Iceland (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - India -“Pictorial Agra” (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - India - photographs with descriptions (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - India - invitations -Flemings’ tour of India, 1959 - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - India - Bhubaneswar, Puri, Konarak; Khajuraho; India Tourism Information (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - India - brochures - Agra, Ajarta/Ellora Caves; Banaras, Bombay, Calcutta, Darjeeling (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - India - Delhi (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Travel Materials
  - India - brochures - Jaipur, Kashmir, Madras, Mysore (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - India - suggested 15 day tour - Government of India Tourist Office (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - India - Tourist map and other information (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - India - World Health, January - February 1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - India - Christmas cards and envelopes (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Norway (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Norway - Festival Programs from 1967 (Festspillene I Bergen) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Norway - 2 booklets, article on Denna and Doris Fleming with accompanying letter, July 9, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Turkey - postcards of Istanbul (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - United States - postcards from the northwest coast (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Menu from Cunard White Star M.V. Georgic, Saturday July 2, 1938; 2 photographs on board RMS “Queen Elizabeth” September 9 - 14, 1954 to New York (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Written account of 1932 trip to Geneva and Europe (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sketchbook - Oversize (Box 14, Folder 1)